<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<messagebundle>
  <msg name="task_number">Number of tasks shown</msg>
  <msg name="green_sort">Green state sorted by</msg>
  <msg name="green_sort_ratio">ratio</msg>
  <msg name="green_sort_date">date</msg>
  <msg name="show_state">Show state</msg>
  <msg name="show_name">Show name</msg>
  <msg name="show_details">Show details</msg>
  <msg name="show_priority">Show priority</msg>
  <msg name="show_date">Show date</msg>
  <msg name="show_time">Show time</msg>
  <msg name="date_format">Date Format</msg>
  <msg name="add_task_img">http://prioritized-task-list.googlecode.com/svn/trunk/add_task.gif</msg>
  <msg name="help_img">http://prioritized-task-list.googlecode.com/svn/trunk/help.gif</msg>
  <msg name="default_task_name">Task name</msg>
  <msg name="non_recurring">non_recurring</msg>
  <msg name="edit">Edit</msg>
  <msg name="vital_task">Vital</msg>
  <msg name="critical_task">Critical</msg>
  <msg name="important_task">Important</msg>
  <msg name="normal_task">Normal</msg>
  <msg name="unimportant_task">Unimportant</msg>
  <msg name="unnecessary_task">Unnecessary</msg>
  <msg name="every_day">every_day</msg>
  <msg name="every_week">every_week</msg>
  <msg name="every_month">every_month</msg>
  <msg name="every_year">every_year</msg>
  <msg name="cancel_edit">Cance Edit</msg>
  <msg name="name_label">Name</msg>
  <msg name="priority_label">Priority</msg>
  <msg name="unnecessary_note">Note: Unnecessary tasks will not escalate to a red state and will automaticly&lt;br&gt; complete once the completion time is reached.</msg>
  <msg name="complete_by_label">Complete by</msg>
  <msg name="am">am</msg>
  <msg name="pm">pm</msg>
  <msg name="repeating_label">Repeating</msg>
  <msg name="repeating_yes">Yes</msg>
  <msg name="repeating_no">No</msg>
  <msg name="recurrence_label">Recurrence</msg>
  <msg name="recurrence_every_day">Every Day</msg>
  <msg name="recurrence_every_week">Every Week</msg>
  <msg name="recurrence_every_month">Every Month</msg>
  <msg name="recurrence_every_year">Every Year</msg>
  <msg name="time_info_first">Number of </msg>
  <msg name="time_info_days">Days</msg>
  <msg name="time_info_hours">Hours</msg>
  <msg name="time_info_last">ahead of time I want to start thinking about or start working on this task</msg>
  <msg name="details_label">Details</msg>
  <msg name="back_button">Back</msg>
  <msg name="help_help">Help</msg>
  <msg name="help_state_info">State Info</msg>
  <msg name="help_priority_info">Priority Info</msg>
  <msg name="help_sorting_info">Sorting Info</msg>
  <msg name="help_language_info">Language Info</msg>
  <msg name="states_states">States</msg>
  <msg name="states_header">There are four states which a task can be in</msg>
  <msg name="states_green_text">The green state is a non urgent state which indicates that the task does not yet need attention.</msg>
  <msg name="states_yellow_text">The yellow state is the warning state. A task enters into this state when the warning time specified when creating the task is reached. At this point the task should be given some attention.</msg>
  <msg name="states_red_text">The red state is the critical state. A task enters into this state when 75% or more of the warning time has elapsed and the task has not been completed. At this point the task should be completed soon or else the target completion time may be missed.</msg>
  <msg name="states_black_text">The black state is the missed state. This state is achieved when a task has gone past it’s completion date without being completed.</msg>
  <msg name="priorities_priorities">Priorities</msg>
  <msg name="priorities_header">There are six different levels of priority which can affect how your tasks are sorted. They are:</msg>
  <msg name="priorities_footer">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Unnecessary&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; task is a special task which will act a little different from the other tasks. 
Unnecessary tasks will not turn to red or black, but will remain yellow even when the critical state is hit. 
It will also automatically be checked off when the completion time is hit.</msg>
  <msg name="sorting_sorting">Sorting:</msg>
  <msg name="sorting_text">All tasks are first sorted by their states. Missed tasks will appear first followed by critical, 
warning and finally the non urgent tasks. Once the tasks have been separated and ordered into their states, 
if a task is in the missed, critical or warning states, the task is first sorted first by priority and then 
by completion time. This means any task that has a higher priority will appear first even if it’s completion 
time is later then some of the others. The non-urgent tasks can be sorted one of two ways depending on a 
config setting.  The first way is by date. This option will sort the tasks strictly by their completion date. 
The second option is to sort by 'ratio'. This option will sort the tasks by a ratio of (time scedualed to now) 
/ (now to the warning time). This will cause tasks to be placed at the bottom of the task list and bubble up 
to the top at different rates, depending on how often they occur or how long ago they were scheduled.  By 
default non-urgent tasks are sorted by “date” to make it easier to understand, but I encourage you to try the 
'ratio’ sort.</msg>
  <msg name="lang_lang">Languages/Date Formats</msg>
  <msg name="lang_lang_text">I currently only support English and Japanese. If you'd like additional laguages or would like to 
                        try translate for another language, please update the gadgets message board.</msg>
  <msg name="lang_date_text">Currently I support MM/DD/YYYY, and DD/MM/YYYY. Let me know if there are any other fromats you wish to see and I'll add them.</msg>
  <msg name="add_new_task">Add a new task</msg>
  <msg name="add_task">Add Task</msg>
  <msg name="update_task">Update </msg>
  <msg name="update_button">Update Task</msg>
  <msg name="remove_button">Remove Task</msg>
</messagebundle> 
